# **ROHAN GADEKAR**

Head of Digital Marketing

# **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Self-taught with 7+ years of experience in Digital marketing, including Search engine optimization, website quality audit, competitor analysis, SEO audits, content marketing, social media marketing, brand awareness campaign, creative content marketing campaign and more.

Increased leads from 35/month to 150+/month organically in a present company.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### PUNE UNIVERSITY

bachelor of computer science 2010 - 2013

# **CERTIFICATIONS | COURSES**

- Google Analytics certification
- Google tag manager certification
- Ryan Stewart SEO training <u>blueprint</u>
- Yoast SEO training
- GMB SEO Local client takeover
- Glen Allsopp SEO blueprint
- Russell Brunson -Funnelology Masterclass

# **SKILLS & COMPETENCIES**

- Building a team from scratch
- Developing digital marketing strategies
- Search engine optimization
- Social Media marketing
- Competitive analysis
- Website quality audits
- Proficient in English, Hindi, Marathi

# **INTEREST**

- Learning new skills
- Research
- Traveling
- · Problem solving
- Reading blogs

# **Experience**

## O Prudour Pvt. Ltd.

**Head of Digital Marketing (2022-Present)** 

- Build a team from scratch, leading a team of 11 marketers and additional content writers.
- Ideated and executed Search engine optimization strategy.
- Creating SOP's and developing systems for a team.
- creating content marketing campaign to acquire authoritative links, Successfully acquired contextual link from DR 80+ website's.
- Email Outreach for acquiring the high authoritative links.
- Increasing organic lead flow from 35/ month to 150+/month in eight months.
- Generating leads from google news approved websites.
- · Working on PR news campaign's as well.

## What a Story LLP

Head of Digital Marketing (2021-2022)

- Coordinated marketing activities amongst 10 team members
- Ideated and executed Digital Marketing Strategy
- Created SEO strategy for a company & international clients
- created a high-quality pitch deck to acquire International Clients for Marketing Services.
- Resolved the UI/UX related issues to increase conversion rate.
- Email Outreach for acquiring the high authoritative links.
- Email Marketing campaigns for existing clients and new leads contributed 7% of sales.
- Created Social media marketing strategies for a company & clients.

#### Vaishadya Oil Industries

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2019-2021)

- Objective generate more sales from the local area.
- Vaishadya, a Pune based company offering cold-pressed oil products. I improved Google my business listing ranking for this company. also run Facebook ad campaigns for branding and sale generation

## Zeus Fitness

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2019-2020)

- Objective Website creation and gain more visibility in google my business listing.
- Zeus Fitness, a Pune based company offering personal fitness training services. I
  designed their website from scratch and also improved Google my business
  listing ranking.

#### Mahaveer Marble Pvt. Ltd.

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2019-2021)

- Objective Generate targeted leads from Google SERP.
- In a span of 12 months, I improved the ranking of the website for the product based keywords. The site now receives an average of 10-12 leads a day. The work responsibilities handled for Mahaveer Marble have been detailed below:
  - Market Research and competitive analysis
  - In-Depth Keyword Research
  - Implemented On-Page SEO strategies
  - Link acquisition Campaign
  - Content Marketing Strategy for youtube

## **FAVOURITE BOOKS**







#### CONTACT

Mobile: 9850 106 174 | 8788 106 174 Email: rohangadekarseo@gmail.com Address: Tukai darshan, lane no. 8 herambh heights, flat no. 9 pune

412308

# Acme dental lounge

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2018-2019)

- · Objective Get more Patients Booking
- My approach was to create the Lead generation website and rank for the buyer intent local keyword in google SERP and google my business. I have ranked the website on the 1st page for the main local keyword dentist in Aundh in Google SERP and google my business listing. The acme dental lounge receives monthly 90-120 leads a month. The work responsibilities handled for Acme dental Lounge have been detailed below:
  - Website Development from scratch
  - · Page speed optimization
  - Implemented On-Page SEO strategies
  - Competitive analysis
  - Link acquisition campaign
  - NAP Audit & building
  - · GMB optimization
  - Conversion rate optimization
  - o Online Reputation Management
  - · Monitored the PPC Campaign

# Capt. Yogiraj Khanwelkar - motivational speaker

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2018-2019)

- Objective generate engagement and building fan-base using Facebook ads(personal branding)
- My approach is to do video-based Facebook marketing to create awareness and engage with the audience. I have done the in-depth topic research based on the pain points. And made videos based on it. I have run the Facebook campaign and optimize the ads to get the best results in a low budget. We have got 6k+ share's in total, close to 1M video views and 2k+ engaging fans and lots of inquiries for talks.

#### Sunburn Festival

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2017-2018)

- Objective Reach to the targeted audience to sell tickets.
- My approach is to target the right audience using paid social media marketing. I
  have run the Instagram and Facebook marketing campaigns. I re-targeted the
  audience based on the awareness campaign data. The event was sold out within
  2 weeks.

# Bold Marketing Pvt. Ltd.

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2016-2018)

- Objective Generate targeted leads from Google SERP.
- Bold marketing is an event management company in Pune I improved the ranking of the website for the buyer intent keywords in google SERP and Google my business. The work responsibilities handled for Bold Marketing have been detailed below:
  - Page speed optimization
  - Implemented On-Page SEO strategies
  - · Competitive analysis
  - Link acquisition campaign
  - NAP Audit & building
  - GMB optimization
  - Conversion rate optimization

# Incorpedia Legal Solutions LLP

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2015-2016)

- Objective Generate targeted leads from Google SERP.
- I was responsible for generating leads and client acquisition. In a span of 12 months, I improved the rankings of the website; currently, it ranks number one in the SERP. The site now receives an average of 8-9 leads a week.

# Private blog network Service

Digital Marketer (Freelance) (2015-2016)

I used to build and sell private blog websites on a marketplace called konker.io I scraped the expired domain with a good link profile using tools like scrapebox and domcop. And Setup the blog on it.